UTU Vice-President's Office George W. Legg Subject Files 5589
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UTU Vice-President's Office George W. Legg Subject Files
1968-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Transportation Union (UTU)
Legg, George W.
5589
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents), correspondence, collective labor agreements.
UTU agreements, reports and correspondence.
8230055
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 03, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 20, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Legg, George W.; AFL-CIO; Chicago and North Western Railway Company; Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Company; Louisville and Nashville Railroad Company; Norfolk and Western Railway Company; Southern Pacific Railroad Company; Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Company; Penn Central Railroad; Pittsburgh & West Virginia Railway Company; United Transportation Union
8230055
- B-P (Box 1)
  - Background Reports, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agreements, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO Internal Disputes Plan, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bus Correspondence, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Merger Committees, Burlington Northern, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chicago and North Western Railway Company Agreement, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Circular Letters, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - United Transportation Union Convention, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Engineers, National Agreements, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Erie Lackawanna Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Free Transportation, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - International Association of General Chairmen, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Laws, Lawsuits, To Be Used in Addressing General Committees, 1962-1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - GS&T Monthly Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer's Monthly Reports, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Job Protection, Advisory Committee, BLE, BLF&E, BRT, ORC&B, SUNA, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Health and Welfare, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Holiday Pay Awards, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Insurance Merger, United Transportation Union, IA, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Locals, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Membership by Locals, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, Representation NMB R-4206, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - NRAB, First Division Five Chiefs' Rulings, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Organizers, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Mediation Agreements (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Southern Pacific Railroad Operating Crafts, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Illinois Central Strike, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Public Law Boards, Third Party Notice, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Penn Central Crew Consist, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Picketing and Strikes, 1963-1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Pittsburgh and West Virginia, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Scope and Contents
    April 19 1968
  - Disputes Account Promulgation of Rules, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    January 13 1972
  - Public Law Boards, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Protective Programs, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Public Law Boards, Procedure, etc., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- R-W (Box 2)
  - Strike Information, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Contains a bound booklet
  - Railway Labor Act, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Special Instructions to Field Service Department from Charles Luna, President, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Training Programs, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Urban Mass Transportation Act, 1964-1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - United Transportation Union, 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Vacations, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Wage Rules, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Wage Movement, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Agreements of the Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Conductors National Wage Rules Dispute Agreement, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Engineers UTU National Wage Agreement. March and April 1969.
  - Western Maryland Railroad. Committee and Carrier Section 6 Notices, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)